swarmcdn.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy | Swarmify Unlimited Video CDN & Hosting

**Swarmify and its associated data processors are fully compliant with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).**

Effective June 14, 2018

We, Swarmify, are committed to protecting any data that we collect concerning you.

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from swarmify.com (the “Site”).

 **Protecting your privacy**

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service. We do not currently, nor will we in the future, sell your personal data.

 **Information Collected**

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”

We also collect Personal Information you give us when you attempt to make a purchase on the Site. This Personal Information depends on the type of service, support, or sale inquiry, and may include your name, address, telephone number, fax number and email address, dates of service provided, types of service provided, payment history, manner of payment, amount of payments, date of payments, domain name, credit card or other payment information. The financial information will be transferred only be used to bill you for the products and services you purchased. If you purchase by credit card, this information may be forwarded to your credit card provider. All sensitive information is collected on a secure server and data is transferred . When transferring personal information a security icon will appear in your browser.

 **Information Use**

This information is used for billing and to provide service and support to our customers. We may also study this information to determine our customers’ needs and provide support for our customers. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorized access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account details. Swarmify may email its monthly newsletter to the primary contact e-mail on file, but customers are able to opt out of this newsletter at any time.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), advertise/retarget, and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

 **  
Log Files**

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site and servers, track access, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. It is possible that personal information about a customer may be included in the log files due to the normal functions of IP addresses and Web browsing.

 **Cookies**

Your Internet browser has the in-built facility for storing small text files – “cookies” – that hold information which allows a website to recognize your account. We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on the Site. More information about cookies can be found at http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie.

 **Disclosing Information**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.

We may use personal information to keep in contact with you and inform you of developments associated with our business. We may also disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to potential partners, our affiliates, and reputable third parties. For example, we use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site. 

You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: <https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/>

You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [ https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

We take all available measures to select affiliates and service providers that are ethical and provide similar privacy protection to their customers and the community. We do not make any representations about the practices and policies about these companies.

 **Use of Intercom Services**

We use third-party analytics services to help understand your usage of our services. In particular, we provide a limited amount of your information (such as sign-up date and some personal information like your email address) to Intercom, Inc. (“Intercom”) and utilize Intercom to collect data for analytics purposes when you visit our website or use our product. As a data processor acting on our behalf, Intercom analyzes your use of our website and/or product and tracks our relationship by way of cookies and similar technologies so that we can improve our service to you. For more information on Intercom’s use of cookies, please visit https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#cookie-policy. We may also use Intercom as a medium for communications, either through email, or through messages within our product(s). As part of our service agreements, Intercom collects publicly available contact and social information related to you, such as your email address, gender, company, job title, photos, website URLs, social network handles and physical addresses, to enhance your user experience. For more information on the privacy practices of Intercom, please visit https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy. Intercom’s services are governed by Intercom’s terms of use which can be found at https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#terms. If you would like to opt out of having this information collected by or submitted to Intercom, please contact us.

 **Behavioral Advertising**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of our targeted advertising by visiting:

<https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads>

and

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

 **Do Not Track**

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

 **Your Rights**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.  Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

 **Data Retention**

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

 **Minors**

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 16.

 **Opt Out & Modifications**

By default, customers do receive any voluntary system updates, such as the newsletters, invoices, and mailings. Any customer who voluntarily receives these updates may unsubscribe at any time. Customers may not opt out of possibly receiving important system notifications, in the rare event that such notification would be necessary.

 **Security**

Swarmify uses technical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. Swarmify uses security measures including and not limited to: physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. When we ask customers or users to provide financial information (such as a credit card number) that data is protected using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology.

 **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about Users upon valid request by government or law officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect your property and rights, or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or stop activity we consider illegal or unethical.

 **Changes to this Policy**

Any changes to our Privacy Policy will be placed here and will supersede this version of our Policy. We will take reasonable steps to draw your attention to any changes in our Policy. However, to be on the safe side, we suggest that you read this document each time you use the website to ensure that it still meets with your approval.

 **Contacting Us**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact our Data Protection Officer, Philip Arambula, by e-mail at [privacy@swarmify.com](mailto:privacy@swarmify.com)
